Guide to the E. Ethelbert Miller papers, 1936-2021, bulk 1962-2018 MS2215
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Ethelbert Miller materials, 1962-2018; 1940-2021; Series 1; Miller, E. Ethelbert
  - Poet files, 1969-2009; 1969-2020; Series 1 Subseries 2
    - Renegade, D.J.: works by, 1999 (Box 43, Folder 16)
    - Reno, Janet, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 106, Folder 12)
    - Reynolds, Craig, 1987; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 106, Folder 13)
    - Reynolds, Elizabeth, 1990; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 106, Folder 14)
    - Rhett, Walter, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 106, Folder 15)
    - Rhodes, Jewell P., 1992; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 107, Folder 1)
    - Rhodes, Jewell: correspondence, promotional materials, clippings, 1993-1997 (Box 44, Folder 1)
    - Rich, Adriennce, 1981, 1993-1996; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 107, Folder 2)
    - Rich, Adrienne: correspondence, articles, 1977-1981 (Box 44, Folder 2)
    - Richards, Phillip M., 1996-2000; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 107, Folder 3)
    - Richards, Vanessa, 1996-1999; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 107, Folder 4)
    - Richardson, Mattie, 1995; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 107, Folder 5)
    - Rickford, Russell: correspondence, 1997-1999 (Box 44, Folder 3)
    - Ridley, Chauncey, 1993-1994; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 107, Folder 6)
    - Riley, Raymond, 1994; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 107, Folder 7)
    - Ripley, Wendy, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 107, Folder 8)
    - Roach-Quarles, Deidra, 1977-1982, 1993-1997; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 107, Folder 9)
    - Robbins, Zachary, 1994; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 107, Folder 10)
    - Roberts, Ama, 1983-1993; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 107, Folder 11)
    - Roberts, Kim: correspondence, works by, 1986-2001 (Box 44, Folder 4)
    - Roberts, Sybil, 1986-1987, 2001; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 108, Folder 1)
    - Robinson, Anike Ciatta, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 108, Folder 2)
    - Robinson, James, 1994; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 108, Folder 3)
    - Robinson, Jeanette D., 1982, 1996-1998; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 108, Folder 4)
    - Robinson, Karyn, 1992; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 108, Folder 5)
    - Rodgers, Ted, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 108, Folder 6)
    - Rodriguez, Luis J., 1991-1992; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 108, Folder 7)
    - Rodriguez, Stacy, 1998; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 108, Folder 8)
    - Rose, Jennifer, 1995; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 108, Folder 9)
    - Rosenfeld, Stephanie, 1993; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 108, Folder 10)
    - Rosenthal, Mel, 1995; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 108, Folder 11)
    - Rossiter, Charles, 1998-1999; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 108, Folder 12)
    - Rutledge, Anne G., 1988, 1995; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 108, Folder 13)
    - Rux, Carl, 1997; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 108, Folder 14)
    - Ryan, Michael: correspondence, works by, 1983-1987 (Box 44, Folder 5)
    - Saakana, Amon Saba, 1988; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 108, Folder 15)
    - Saalakhan, Mauri, 1982-1987, 1997; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 108, Folder 16)
    - Sabir, Wanda, 1992-1995; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 108, Folder 17)
    - Sadin, Marjie, 1984; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 108, Folder 18)
    - Sagel, Jim, 1984; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 108, Folder 19)
    - Salaam, Kalamu Ya, 1996; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 108, Folder 20 (1/2))
    - Salaam, Kalamu Ya, 1983, 1994; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 108, Folder 2 (2/2))
    - Salimu, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 109, Folder 1)
    - Saliym, Abdul, 1990; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 109, Folder 2)
    - Salkey, Andrew, 1995 May 16; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 109, Folder 3)
    - Sallah, Tijan M., 1989-1993; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 109, Folder 4)
    - Saloy, Mona Lisa, 1994-1995; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 109, Folder 5)
    - Saloy, Mona Lisa, 2005 August 5; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 172, Folder 6)
    - Samuel, Marcia, 1994; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 109, Folder 6)
    - Sam's World, 1977; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 191, Folder 6)
    - Sanchez, Sonia: articles, profiles, 1988-2003 (Box 44, Folder 6)
    - Sanchez, Sonia: plays, poems, other material, 1971-2002 (Box 44, Folder 7)
    - Sanchez, Sonia: correspondence, undated (Box 44, Folder 8)
    - Sanchez, Sonia: promotional material (Box 44, Folder 9)
    - Sanders, Victoria, 1994-1997; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 109, Folder 7)
    - Sandler, Kathe: "A Question of Color", 1986-1993; Series Subseries 2 (Box 171, Folder 4)
    - Sandy, Stephen, 1988; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 109, Folder 8)
    - Sapphire: reviews, 1996 (Box 44, Folder 10)
    - Sargent, Robert, 1995; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 109, Folder 9)
    - Sarvan, Charles, 1997; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 109, Folder 10)
    - Satiafa, 1982; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 109, Folder 11)
    - Saunders, Melvina, 1992, 1995; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 109, Folder 12)
    - Scales-Trent, Judy, 1995; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 109, Folder 13)
    - Schowers, Mario, 1982-1983; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 109, Folder 14)
    - Scott, Barbara, 1997; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 109, Folder 15)
    - Scott, W. Clayton, 2006 October 18; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 109, Folder 16)
    - Scott, Joseph W., 2001; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 110, Folder 1 (1/3))
    - Scott, Joseph W., 2001; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 110, Folder 2 (2/3))
    - Scott, Joseph W., 2001; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 110, Folder 3 (3/3))
    - Scott, Linda, 1983 May; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 110, Folder 4)
    - Scott, Stephen, 1991, 1995; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 110, Folder 5)
    - Sealey, Joseph, 1985; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 110, Folder 6)
    - Seals, Tianna: correspondence, 1987-1992 (Box 44, Folder 11)
    - Seaton, Sandra, 1989, 1999; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 110, Folder 7)
    - Secundy, Marian Gray, 1986; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 111, Folder 1)
    - Seibles, Timothy: correspondence, 1994 (Box 44, Folder 12)
    - Seidel, Ethan, 1991-1992; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 111, Folder 2)
    - Sekou, Lasana, 1986-1991; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 111, Folder 3)
    - Sellers, April Maria, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 111, Folder 4)
    - Service, Denise, 1981-1984; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 111, Folder 5)
    - Seyler, Deborah, 1983-1987; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 111, Folder 6)
    - Shallal, Andy, 2006; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 111, Folder 7)
    - Shange, Ntozake, 1976-1982; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 111, Folder 8)
    - Shankar, Ravi: works by, correspondence (Box 44, Folder 13)
    - Shannon, Angela, 2003; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 111, Folder 9)
    - Shannon, Joy, 1985; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 111, Folder 10)
    - Shannon, Sandra: correspondence, 1990-1993 (Box 45, Folder 1)
    - Shannon, Sandra: works by, 1989-1996 (Box 45, Folder 2)
    - Shannon, Sandra: miscellaneous (Box 45, Folder 3)
    - Sharfstein, Daniel, 1990; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 111, Folder 11)
    - Sharp, Saundra: correspondence, works by, 1986-1993 (Box 45, Folder 4)
    - Sharpe, Alan, 1991-1992; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 111, Folder 12 (1/2))
    - Sharpe, Alan, 1991-1992; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 111, Folder 13 (2/2))
    - Shea, Renee, 1997; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 124, Folder 16)
    - Shelton, Richard, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 112, Folder 1 (1/2))
    - Shelton, Richard, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 112, Folder 2 (2/2))
    - Shepherd, Ambrosia, 1990; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 112, Folder 3)
    - Shirley, Aleda, 1991 July 15; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 112, Folder 4)
    - Shonekan, D., 1989-1992; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 112, Folder 5)
    - Shore, Jane, 1998; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 112, Folder 6)
    - Shreve, Susan, 1989-1993; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 112, Folder 7)
    - Shumaker, Peggy: correspondence, promotional material, 1990-1992 (Box 45, Folder 5)
      This folder is closed for 50 years from date of donation, 2009.
    - Shuman, Michael, 1992-1994; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 112, Folder 8)
    - Simmerman, Jim, 1994; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 112, Folder 9)
    - Simmons, Aishah S., 1995-1996; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 112, Folder 10)
    - Simon, Maurya, 1994-1995; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 112, Folder 11)
    - Singleton, Giovanni, 1995, 2001; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 112, Folder 12)
    - Singleton, Giovanni: correspondence, 1996-1999 (Box 45, Folder 6)
    - Singleton, Giovanni: works by, 1999 (Box 45, Folder 7)
    - Skeeter, Sharyn: correspondence, works by, 1984-1988 (Box 45, Folder 8)
    - Skeeter, Sharyn: correspondence, works by, interview, 1988-1995 (Box 45, Folder 9)
    - Sklarew, Myra: correspondence, clippings, 1988-1992 (Box 45, Folder 10)
    - Slaughter, Jocelyn: correspondence, 1980-1983 (Box 45, Folder 11)
    - Smith, Anna D., 1992; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 112, Folder 13)
    - Smith, Betty, 1982; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 112, Folder 14)
    - Smith, Carlton E., 1987; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 112, Folder 15)
    - Smith, Dean, 1998; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 112, Folder 16)
    - Smith, Kweli, 1988-1992; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 112, Folder 17)
    - Smith, Michael, 1982-1984; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 112, Folder 18)
    - Smith, Patricia, 1995; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 112, Folder 19)
    - Snodgrass, Ann, 1991-1992; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 112, Folder 20)
    - Snowdgrass, Ann: correspondence, works by, 1986-1992 (Box 45, Folder 12)
    - Snow, Tonya, 1995; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 113, Folder 1)
    - Snyder, Gary, 1995-1996; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 113, Folder 2)
    - Sokenu, Julius Olusola, 1992; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 113, Folder 3)
    - Solomon, Dorothy, 1985 or 1995; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 113, Folder 4)
    - Solomon, Sylvia, 1994-1995; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 113, Folder 5)
    - Sorrells-Adewale, E.H., 1981-1989; Series subseries 2 (Box 171, Folder 5)
    - Souffrant, Leah, 2003; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 113, Folder 6)
    - Southwood, Anthony, 2008; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 124, Folder 17)
    - Spears, Alan, 1990-1991; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 113, Folder 7)
    - Spellman, A.B.: biography, cirriculum vitae, resume, 1987-1994 (Box 45, Folder 13)
    - Spellman, A.B.: works by, 2001 (Box 45, Folder 14)
    - Spence, Dorothy, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 113, Folder 8)
    - Spicer, Eloise, 1981 August; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 113, Folder 9)
    - Srinivsan, Manglam: correspondence, 1992-1994 (Box 46, Folder 1)
    - Srinivasan, Sarayu, 1993-1995; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 113, Folder 10)
    - St. John, Bruce, 1972 December; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 113, Folder 11)
    - St. John, Primus, 1994-1995; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 113, Folder 12)
    - Stafford, William, 1993-1994; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 113, Folder 13)
    - Stanley, Thomas, 1991-1999; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 113, Folder 14)
    - Stauffer, Jill: correspondence, works by, 1986-1987 (Box 46, Folder 2)
    - Steel, Lewis M., 1998; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 113, Folder 15 (1/2))
    - Steel, Lewis M., 1998; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 113, Folder 16 (2/2))
    - Steele, Jennifer, 2007; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 114, Folder 1)
    - Steinem, Robert, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 114, Folder 2)
    - Steptoe, Lamont B., 1986-1988, 1993; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 114, Folder 3)
    - Sternburg, Janet, 1979; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 114, Folder 4)
    - Stinson, Susan, Undated; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 172, Folder 5)
    - Stocker-Edwards, Stanley, 2006; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 114, Folder 5)
    - Stocker-Edwards, Stanley, 2004 November 14; Series 1 Subseries2 (Box 172, Folder 4)
    - Stokes, Daniel, 1982; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 114, Folder 6)
    - Stokes, William, 1980; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 114, Folder 7)
    - Stokes, William: correspondence, works by [1 of 3], 1977 (Box 46, Folder 3)
    - Stokes, William: correspondence, works by, 1978 (Box 46, Folder 4)
    - Stokes, William: correspondence, works by, 1977-1978 (Box 46, Folder 5)
    - Stover, Darrel: promotional material, 1987-1997 (Box 46, Folder 6)
    - Strange, Sharon, 1990 August 27; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 114, Folder 8)
    - Straus, Joy, 1994-1995; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 114, Folder 9)
    - Straw, Silvana: correspondence, works by, 1993 (Box 46, Folder 7)
    - Strayhorn, Gail, 1976; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 114, Folder 10)
    - Stroblas, Laurie, 1994-2000; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 114, Folder 11 (1/2))
    - Stroblas, Laurie, 1994-2000; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 114, Folder 12 (2/2))
    - Stroude, Andrew, 1991; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 114, Folder 13)
    - Stuckey, Elma (Sterling), 1975; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 114, Folder 14)
    - Suandi, 1984-1985; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 114, Folder 15)
    - Sullivan, May Miller: promotional material, 1985-1986 (Box 46, Folder 8)
    - Sullivan, May Miller: profiles, articles, 1982-1995 (Box 46, Folder 9)
    - Sullivan, May Miller: interviews, 1987 (Box 46, Folder 10)
    - Sullivan, May Miller: works by, 1986 (Box 46, Folder 11)
    - Sullivan, May Miller: miscellaneous, 1988-2005 (Box 46, Folder 12)
    - Sundiata, Sekou, 1989-2007; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 114, Folder 16)
    - Sutton, Fedora, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 115, Folder 1)
    - Swenson, Karen, 1988-1989, 1993; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 115, Folder 2)
    - Sykes, Roberta, 1995-1996; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 115, Folder 3)
    - Tait, George Edward, 1984; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 115, Folder 4)
    - Tallent, Elizabeth: correspondence, 1985 (Box 46, Folder 13)
    - Tallie, Mariahadessa, 1996-1999; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 115, Folder 5)
    - Tarpley, Natasha, 1991-1995; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 115, Folder 6)
    - Tate, Brian: correspondence, works by, promotional material, 1991-1994 (Box 46, Folder 14)
    - Tate, Caron, 1980, 1987; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 115, Folder 7)
    - Tate, Claudia: promotional materials, 1987-1993 (Box 47, Folder 1)
    - Tate, Claudia: profiles, articles, 1983 (Box 47, Folder 2)
    - Tate, Claudia: correspondence, 1986-1999 (Box 47, Folder 3)
    - Tate, Claudia: reviews, 1983 (Box 47, Folder 4)
    - Tate, Claudia: works by (Box 47, Folder 5)
    - Tate, Claudia: miscellaneous, 1983-2001 (Box 47, Folder 6)
    - Tate, Garth, 1982-1995; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 115, Folder 8)
    - Tate, Gregory, 1981-1989, 1994-1999; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 115, Folder 9)
    - Tate, Greg: works by, 1977-2002 (Box 47, Folder 7)
    - Tate, Sonsyrea: works by clippings, 1996-1997 (Box 47, Folder 8)
    - Taylor, Anita D., 2001; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 115, Folder 10)
    - Taylor, Gary, 1995; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 115, Folder 11)
    - Taylor, Henry, 1995-1996; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 115, Folder 12)
    - Teasley, Lisa, 1989-1995; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 115, Folder 13)
    - Teasley, Lisa: articles, correspondence, 2002 (Box 47, Folder 10)
    - Tecza, Rachael, 1994; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 115, Folder 14)
    - Terrell, Beverly Dee, 1990, 1995; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 115, Folder 15)
    - Terrell, Vincent, 1969-1970; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 115, Folder 16)
    - Terry, Linda, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 116, Folder 1)
    - Tham, Hilary: correspondence, works by, 1985 (Box 47, Folder 9)
    - Thomas, Barbara, 1980; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 116, Folder 2)
    - Thomas, Colette, 1994; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 116, Folder 3)
    - Thomas, Susann, 1976, 1979; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 116, Folder 4)
    - Thomas, Truth, Undated; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 172, Folder 3)
    - Thompson, Chezia B., 1980-1995; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 116, Folder 5 (1/3))
    - Thompson, Chezia B., 1980-1995; Series 1 Subserie 2 (Box 116, Folder 6 (2/3))
    - Thompson, Chezia B., 1980-1995; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 116, Folder 7 (3/3))
    - Thompson, Julius, 1994-1996; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 117, Folder 1)
    - Thrash, Venus, 1994; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 117, Folder 2)
    - Timpson, Reggie, 1997; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 117, Folder 3)
    - Tiombe, Ayo, 1975; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 117, Folder 4)
    - Tisdale, Gwen Wood, 1987; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 117, Folder 5)
    - Tolliver, Imani, 1994-1997; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 117, Folder 6)
    - Tosca, Bobbie, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 117, Folder 7)
    - Towner, De Tannyia, 1998; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 117, Folder 8)
    - Trapp, Tobias: correpsondence, works by, 1997-2001 (Box 47, Folder 11)
    - Traylor, Eleanor, 1987-1990; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 117, Folder 9)
    - Trethewey, Natasha: correspondence, works by, 1994 (Box 47, Folder 12)
    - Troupe, Quincy, 1978-2003; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 117, Folder 10)
    - Tsang, Lori: bio, correspondence, 1999-2000 (Box 47, Folder 13)
    - Tsang, Lori: works by, 1996-1999 (Box 47, Folder 14)
    - Tsang, Lori: cirriculum vitae, programs, interviews, articles, promotional material, 1997-1999 (Box 47, Folder 15)
    - Tucker, Liza, 1984 June 7; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 117, Folder 11)
    - Tucker, Mike, 1987-1992, 2005; 1987-1992; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 124, Folder 18)
    - Tuckey, Melissa: works by, undated (Box 48, Folder 1)
    - Turner, Seneca, 1994-1995; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 117, Folder 12)
    - Tutuola, Amos, 1983; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 117, Folder 13)
    - Udechukwu, Ada: works by, correspondence, 1999-2003 (Box 48, Folder 2)
    - Udechukwu, Obiora, 1981, 1988-1989; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 117, Folder 14)
    - Umoja, Nailah Folami, 1997; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 117, Folder 15)
    - Upton, Elaine, 1993-2004; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 117, Folder 16)
    - Uribe, Kirmen, 2006; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 117, Folder 17)
    - Vann, Stephanie, 1997; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 118, Folder 1)
    - Vargas, Roberto, 1982-1983; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 118, Folder 2)
    - Vega, Elizabeth, 1985; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 118, Folder 3)
    - Velazquez, Maria, After 2006; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 118, Folder 4)
    - Venus, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 118, Folder 5)
    - Verdelle, A.J.: works by, articles, 1985-1995 (Box 48, Folder 3)
    - Vest, Jennifer, 1993-1994; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 118, Folder 6)
    - Villarreal, Rebecca: correspondence, works by, promotional materials, 1997-2003 (Box 48, Folder 4)
    - Villarreal, Rebecca: correspondence, works by, 1995-2001 (Box 48, Folder 5)
    - Wade-Gayles, Gloria, 1984-1995; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 118, Folder 7)
    - Walker, Abena, 1974-1975, 1989-1990; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 118, Folder 8)
    - Walker, Alice, 1978-1982; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 125, Folder 1)
    - Walker, Alice: correspondence, 1986-1994 (Box 48, Folder 6)
    - Walker, Alice: interviews, articles, 1983-2000 (Box 48, Folder 7)
    - Walker, Aice: profiles, 1986-2001 (Box 48, Folder 8)
    - Walker, Alice: articles, short stories, 1985-1994 (Box 48, Folder 9)
    - Walker, Alice: The Color Purple reviews, 1985-1993 (Box 48, Folder 10)
    - Walker, Alice: Living By the Word clippings, 1988 (Box 48, Folder 11)
    - Walker, Alice: In Search of Our Mothers' Gardens clippings, 1982 (Box 48, Folder 12)
    - Walker, Alice: You Can't Keep a Good Woman Down clippings, 1981 (Box 48, Folder 13)
    - Walker, Alice: The Temple of My Familiar clippings, 1989 (Box 48, Folder 14)
    - Walker, Kwaku, 1974; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 118, Folder 9)
    - Walker, Margaret, 1975-1999; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 118, Folder 10)
    - Waniek, Marilyn, 1990-1998; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 118, Folder 11)
    - Ward, Jerry: correspondence, works by, promotional material, 1988-2001 (Box 48, Folder 15)
    - Waring, Belle, 1993; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 118, Folder 12)
    - Warner, Rebecca, 2002; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 118, Folder 13)
    - Washington, Kimberly T., Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 118, Folder 14)
    - Washington, Mary Helen: clippings, 1980-1991 (Box 48, Folder 16)
    - Watley, Matthew, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 118, Folder 15)
    - Watson, Dennis, 1981-1983; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 118, Folder 16)
    - Weatherford, Carole, 1994-1995; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 118, Folder 17)
    - Weaver, Afaa: correspondence, 2003-2005 (Box 49, Folder 1)
    - Weaver, Michael: correspondence, 2005 (Box 49, Folder 2)
    - Webb, Eric, 1991-1999; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 118, Folder 18)
    - Webster, Ivan, 1994-1995; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 118, Folder 19)
    - Weimer, Dana, 1994-1995; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 119, Folder 1)
    - Weinstein, David, 1992-1993; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 119, Folder 2)
    - Weinstein, Sharon, 1994-1995; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 119, Folder 3)
    - Welters, Raigan, 1990-1991; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 119, Folder 4)
    - Wesley, Janice, 1990; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 119, Folder 5)
    - Wesley, Valerie, 1994-1995; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 119, Folder 6)
    - West, Cornell: Announcements, 1992-1995; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 119, Folder 7)
    - West, Cornell: Articles, 2002; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 119, Folder 8)
    - West, Cornell: Interviews, 1993; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 119, Folder 9)
    - West, Cornell: Miscellaneous, 1993-2002; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 119, Folder 10)
    - West, Cornell: Profiles, 1991-2002; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 119, Folder 11)
    - West, Cornell: Works By, 1994-1996; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 119, Folder 12)
    - West, Dorothy, 1995; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 119, Folder 13)
    - West, Dorothy: correspondence, works by, 1994-1998 (Box 49, Folder 3)
    - West, Stan, 1993-1996; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 119, Folder 14)
    - Weyhe, Arthur, 1983-1986; Series 1Subseries 2 (Box 171, Folder 6)
    - What the Potter Said, 2005; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 191, Folder 8)
    - Whetstone, Calvin Coolidge (Stoney) - Edited by Marvin Whetstone, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 120, Folder 1)
    - Wickham, John, 1982; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 120, Folder 2)
    - Wilber, Valentine, 1994-1996; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 120, Folder 3)
    - Wiley, Richard: correspondence, curriculum vitae, 1993 (Box 49, Folder 4)
    - Wilkinson, Quintin, 1993; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 120, Folder 4)
    - Willard, Elmo Riley III, 1991; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 120, Folder 5)
    - Williams, Anthony Maurice, 1993; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 120, Folder 6)
    - Williams, Bettye, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 120, Folder 7)
    - Williams, Crystal, 1999; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 120, Folder 8)
    - Williams, Eugene Jr., 1995; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 120, Folder 9)
    - Williams, Gregory Howard, 1995; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 120, Folder 10)
    - Williams, John, 1978-1982, 1999; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 120, Folder 11)
    - Williams, Kimmika, 1987; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 120, Folder 12)
    - Williams, Lana C., 1996; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 120, Folder 13)
    - Williams, Marita, 1983; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 120, Folder 14)
    - Williams, Michael, 1991; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 120, Folder 15)
    - Williams, Mynique, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 120, Folder 16)
    - Williams, Otis: clippings, promotional material, 1984-1997 (Box 49, Folder 5)
    - Williams, Sarah, 1994; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 120, Folder 17)
    - Williams, Terri, 1991; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 120, Folder 18)
    - Williams, Traci Halima, 1985-1987; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 120, Folder 19)
    - Williams, Yolanda, 1987; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 120, Folder 20)
    - Willis, Deborah, 1992-1995, 1999; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 120, Folder 21)
    - Wilson, August: interviews, 1987 (Box 49, Folder 6)
    - Wilson, August: correspondence, undated (Box 49, Folder 7)
    - Wilson, August: "Fences" clippins, 1987 (Box 49, Folder 8)
    - Wilson, August: pofiles, articles, 1995-1996 (Box 49, Folder 9)
    - Wilson, August: promotional materials, 1997-1998 (Box 49, Folder 10)
    - Wilson, August: miscellaneous, undated (Box 49, Folder 11)
    - Wilson, Carletta: correspondence, promotional material, 1988-1994 (Box 49, Folder 12)
    - Wilson, Kimberly, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 120, Folder 22)
    - Wilson, Kimberly, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 121, Folder 1)
    - Winbush, Wanda, 1978-1985; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 121, Folder 2)
    - Winn, Michael Develle, 1994; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 121, Folder 3)